<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Muslim on Laataiasu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/muslim/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Muslim on Laataiasu</description>
    <image>
      <title>Laataiasu</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/muslim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Memory is Unreliable</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2024-02-17-memory-is-unreliable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2024-02-17-memory-is-unreliable/</guid>
      <description>Later, when you greet someone who has forgotten you, don&amp;rsquo;t make her remember you.
You can pretend to be her fan while saying &amp;ldquo;take care&amp;rdquo; as you leave.
Perhaps there is suppressed trauma related to you.
Maybe remembering you will cause her to stop functioning and lose her big idea regarding a new theory or contribution to civilization.
Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;re not that important to her.
Perhaps you are a disgrace/stain in her memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hatred is &#39;Fitrah&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-11-30-hatred-is-fitrah/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-11-30-hatred-is-fitrah/</guid>
      <description>Some gay people flee from Indonesia, and I strongly despise them. They accuse me of homophobia just because I&amp;rsquo;m Muslim, and we insult each other.
Insulting each other is &amp;lsquo;fitrah&amp;rsquo;. A person mocking doesn&amp;rsquo;t realize they are doing so. Examples include: Javanese with a thick accent, Sundanese, Batak&amp;rsquo;s roughness, Malay style like Upin Ipin.
Mocking each other is &amp;lsquo;fitrah&amp;rsquo;; we can&amp;rsquo;t stop it. Tolerance has never existed. The will to mock is the truth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Singer - Ordinary People Are Evil</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-11-30-ordinary-people-are-evil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-11-30-ordinary-people-are-evil/</guid>
      <description>Orang utilitarian gini mirip komunis lemah syahwat, selalu cari silver bullet untuk melengkapi lobang ideologinya. Kalo ga sesuai tinggal potong2 minoritas dan buang outlier selayak procustes tentang apa2 yang ga sesuai sama mereka karena kurang bisa menerima diversitas dan buru-buru ingin perfect. That&amp;rsquo;s why I love them.
Dengan prinsip macam itu, saat mereka ditanya, &amp;ldquo;What makes you happy?&amp;rdquo; Jawaban paling berakhlak dan ethical yang paling dapat diterima harusnya gini:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Surveillence-Driven System to Understand More about Religion Groups</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-11-01-surveillence-relorgs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-11-01-surveillence-relorgs/</guid>
      <description>I simply want to know what makes people enjoy this.
Is it because of the good music?
Is it because of the sense of togetherness?
How much do they really love their prophet?
I suspect that all the people who gather there are proficient in Arabic, which allows them to truly enjoy it.
But my hypothesis is that the combination of any of these factors gives them a sense of flow and perceived enjoyment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowerment, Beauty, and the Shifting Paradigm: A Reflection on Standards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-10-28-beauty-standards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-10-28-beauty-standards/</guid>
      <description>When you throw away the concept and the dimension of time, you&amp;rsquo;ll find that the effort put into grooming yourself is a futile endeavor, contributing to the perpetuation of the &amp;ldquo;halo effect&amp;rdquo; ideology.
We cannot be blind to the innovations in chemistry, pharmaceuticals, marketing, etc., that contribute to shaping our world in this way. Transforming someone from unattractive to beautiful is a form of empowerment.
Much of the progress and growth appears empowering, until it becomes mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Throw your ethics into the trash can!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-10-14-trash-your-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-10-14-trash-your-ethics/</guid>
      <description>If someone automates Instagram to like every account they follow, reply, and comment based on the context of the picture you post, you will find some sort of excitement if that someone is who you like, and otherwise if you don&amp;rsquo;t like. Humans can be easily fooled because of the feature of &amp;lsquo;feeling.&amp;rsquo;
Humans are not multitaskers, but with computers, they can be. Computers resemble the Jutsu of a thousand shadows from Naruto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stagnation of LDK and Many College Organizations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-10-02-the-stagnation-of-ldk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-10-02-the-stagnation-of-ldk/</guid>
      <description>Many LDK/rohis campus or organization in general seem to not be contributing much to the nation, or even to the university, or their respective departments/majors.
@fukifasilkom @gamaisitb @mt_binus etc
They tend to provide unurgent seminars, lack research tailored to the needs of their members, and make little effort to help all members reach their potential.
Most of what they do is conduct seminars that are mostly unhelpful, especially in areas where they lack deep knowledge of their religion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fallacy of Effectiveness and Kemubaziran</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-09-06-fallacy-of-effectiveness-and-mubazir/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-09-06-fallacy-of-effectiveness-and-mubazir/</guid>
      <description>God created all beautiful scenery. What is the purpose of beauty?
And it is never enough. It is like the Alif Lam Mim and the likes Ayat.
Or it is like the &amp;lsquo;yeee hawww&amp;rsquo; from the Jackass.
It indicates that it&amp;rsquo;s not the rational that leads, but the irrational, the redundant, the ineffective.
That is the fallacy where they see others similar to them, so they feel like they are replaceable, unimportant, and useless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sakamoto Unmasked: Navigating Tyranny with Elegance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-09-05-sakamoto-and-replaceable/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-09-05-sakamoto-and-replaceable/</guid>
      <description>Man is mortal; thus, every man is replaceable.
Dependency is something I never force onto someone or any system. If I am somehow needed by someone, I try to help, but not to make them dependent on me. I want everything to be loosely coupled. I want to give every beautiful thing I have and then perish.
For a company, organization, or family, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be seen as irreplaceable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear Budiman Sudjatmiko</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-08-20-dear-budi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-08-20-dear-budi/</guid>
      <description>Untuk Budi,
rather than building &amp;lsquo;BUKIT ALGORITMA&amp;rsquo; the hills of wannabe Silicon Valley algorithms that are centralized, elitist, and stagnant, it&amp;rsquo;s better to develop a mosque-based social credit system like Chongqing. The title is &amp;lsquo;AKSELERASI SMART CITY MELALUI MASJID BERPRESTASI&amp;rsquo; which is more decentralized and prioritizes equal distribution.
It gets boring every time there&amp;rsquo;s a beggar, making it very difficult to verify whether they are genuinely in need or not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musings on Life, Legends, and the Quirks of Human Nature</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-08-17-muhammad-the-legend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-08-17-muhammad-the-legend/</guid>
      <description>You know what Pareto once said, right? It&amp;rsquo;s like he figured out that only 20 percent of folks are doing 80 percent of the cool stuff. The rest of us are stuck with these mind-numbing jobs that could easily be replaced by robots.
Now, speaking of Indonesia, it&amp;rsquo;s a Muslim-majority place, but that whole &amp;ldquo;Isy kariman Au Mutsyahidan&amp;rdquo;, live gloriously or die a martyr thing? Well, it&amp;rsquo;s more of a catchy slogan than anything else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islam and the Data Scientist&#39;s Quest: Seeking Insights Amidst Biases and Mental Models</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-03-01-muslim-and-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-03-01-muslim-and-data-science/</guid>
      <description>data scientist dan the sixth sense movie
&amp;ldquo;I see dead people walking around like regular people, they don&amp;rsquo;t know the are dead&amp;rdquo;
Paranoid, banyak asumsi, banyak interpretasi, ujung-ujungnya simplifikasi sesuatu yang kompleks.
Dari dulu diajarin buat selalu cari pola, cari makna
padahal it&amp;rsquo;s obvious, ga ada makna.
art of clear thinking, daniel kahnemann bias,
sadar bahwa defaultnya manusia itu emang tolol, penuh bias.
Biases arose because they are effective. And effectiveness has always been a virtue favorable to survival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Turkey Problem in Gen-Z</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-02-01-turkey-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 11:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-02-01-turkey-problem/</guid>
      <description>Generation Z is often seen as carefree, facing difficulty in finding jobs, lacking respect for adults, being oversensitive yet savage and brutal, experiencing sexual weaknesses, engaging in deception through social media, adopting a borrowing mentality, having a short attention span, challenging the status quo, dealing with information overload, being exposed to excessive news about corruption, participating in cancel culture, and facing the consequences of global warming. They often associate various issues with mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Suppressed Dream</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-12-25-a-suppressed-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-12-25-a-suppressed-dream/</guid>
      <description>Visi Meningkatkan kesadaran masyarakat akan data driven society
Mimpi Digitalisasi masjid dan tempat ibadah lainnya
Hal yang mungkin dilakukan:
Lewat Rohis (e.g., FUKI FASILKOM UI) Buat program mentoring untuk networking sama anak2 SMA/SMP (Perlu research dulu pada mau ga jadi mentor/mentee) Kasih skill digital, literasi data, akuntansi, bisnis, dll Doktrin buat aktifkan masjid di sekitarnya (digitalisasi masjid) Pendekatan dari masjid terdekat Dalam hal ini saya sudah memiliki fixed mindset :v Sudah gagal dalam sosial di sekitar rumah, kurang punya karakter dan contoh yang baik, dan sepertinya saya perlu jadi orang munafik untuk pendekatan ini jadi malas aja aowkaokwoakwoakw</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kritik, Prioritas, dan Pengambilan Keputusan Ridwan Kamil terhadap Masjid Al-Jabbar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-11-10-kenapa-ridwan-kamil-harus-berterima-kasih-pada-oposisi-pembangunan-masjid-aljabbar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 11:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-11-10-kenapa-ridwan-kamil-harus-berterima-kasih-pada-oposisi-pembangunan-masjid-aljabbar/</guid>
      <description>Bayangin, bertrilyun-trilyun APBD dipake bikin Mesjid di tengah sawah..
..bukannya dipake utk kepentingan semua orang seperti Angkutan Massal Ya gak usah dibayangin, bisa diliat di bawah ini: https://t.co/I7uCMCX8ns
&amp;mdash; :) (@Outstandjing) January 1, 2023 RK seharusnya berterima kasih atas banyaknya kritik yang diterima terkait Masjid Al Jabbar. Ada sebuah hadis yang mengatakan,
لَا تَقُومُ السَّاعَةُ حَتَّى يَتَبَاهَى النَّاسُ فِي الْمَسَاجِدِ Artinya: &amp;ldquo;Kiamat tidak akan terjadi hingga manusia bermegah-megahan dalam membangun masjid,&amp;rdquo; (HR Abu Dawud)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why a Group of People Like to Go to the Mall</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-10-07-why-a-group-of-people-like-to-go-to-the-mall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-10-07-why-a-group-of-people-like-to-go-to-the-mall/</guid>
      <description>You get paid as an employee. After you work you go the mall to enjoy your payment. This similar with some wall street ass in the dark period too, the difference is they go to the prostitution or gambling places. But who&amp;rsquo;s hurting here? No one, except the jealous people who looks people can more enjoy the life itself. In it&amp;rsquo;s substance, every aspect is just the same.
You might think prostitution or gambling is bad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liga Arab, Bani Israil, dan Project Manager Lebah</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-01-04-liga-arab-bani-israil-dan-project-manager-lebah/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-01-04-liga-arab-bani-israil-dan-project-manager-lebah/</guid>
      <description>Liga Arab, Bani Israil, dan Project Manager Lebah Saat pasukan lebah sudah membangun 1/4 sarangnya di plafon rumah anda, anda mungkin bertanya-tanya, mengapa harus di tempat dekat saya tinggal?
Bayangkan apabila PM lebah, entahlah siapa yang ditunjuk ratu lebah, yang memiliki keahlian sebagai PM, atau mungkin dirinya sendiri karena ia merupakan yang paling superior diantara para lebah, sudah merencanakan dengan matang mengenai rencana proyek migrasinya.
Sang PM lebah menginisiasi proyek dengan sangat matang, dari mulai scope, time cost, quality, lebah resource, communication, stakeholder, risk, dan procurement-nya.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penuntut Ilmu Laduni</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-12-10-penuntut-ilmu-laduni/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-12-10-penuntut-ilmu-laduni/</guid>
      <description>Belajar dari bio ig teman saya yang merupakan penganut dan penuntut ilmu laduni,
Setiap postingan berperan pada kesiasiaan penyimpanan cloud. Mari perbanyak bytes, mari andil dalam pemanasan global. Bytes, biner, dan angka tidak penting, mari tunjukan eksistensi anda melalu perbanyakan bytes, mari mubazirkan sumber dan energi yang ada, sebelum yang dapat diperbarui optimal ditemukan, usaha anda untuk terus menguras sumber daya merupakan optimisme bahwa di masa depan resource akan sustain dan dapat selalu teregenerasi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football Manager 2008</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-12-09-fm-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-12-09-fm-2008/</guid>
      <description>Untuk FUKI dan Lembaga Dakwah Lainnya
&amp;ldquo;I never imagined how frustrating weakness can be&amp;rdquo; - Gon
Nonton kuliah Jack Dorsey membuat saya ingat kalo dari dulu saya ingin ngeliat apa yang terjadi setiap sudut dunia. Bukan tentang hal negatif atau hal-hal sepele sepele, tapi ingin terus melihat suatu progress yang bisa dibanggakan dan membantu untuk banyak orang di setiap sudut dunia. Tapi niat baik itu tidak selalu membawa jadi baik juga.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kenapa Harus Tau Crypto, Blockchain, dan sejenisnya</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-07-13-kenapa-harus-tau-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-07-13-kenapa-harus-tau-crypto/</guid>
      <description>secara cocoklogi, kronologi simpelnya kaya gini
masalah lingkungan &amp;gt; pandemi &amp;gt; stimulus US &amp;gt; yang bercukupan bingung naruh uang dimana &amp;gt; influencers/manipulators speak &amp;gt; inflasi aset-aset kripto
…
Kenapa harus tahu crypto Kenapa harus tau crypto, blockchain, dan sejenisnya
.
.
.
Sebelumnya saya agak pesimis tentang perkembangan teknologi. Sebagai anak Sistem Informasi yang dituntut untuk mengefisiensikan apapun, ada dilema moral saat tau masalah terbesar mengembangkan sistem informasi bukan terletak pada teknologinya, melainkan manusianya.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowden Is Not a Hero</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-04-13-snowden-is-not-a-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-04-13-snowden-is-not-a-hero/</guid>
      <description>snowden bukan pahlawan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Process Modeling Organisasi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-04-05-business-process-management-organisasi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-04-05-business-process-management-organisasi/</guid>
      <description>Mengapa setiap organisasi membutuhkan bisnis process modelling? Menyamakan bisnis dengan uang
Outline
Masalahnya adalah tidak ada evaluasi yang benar-benar evaluasi
Bisnis pada kenyataannya semuanya adalah bisnis, namun sering dianggap tabu proses rumah sakit dianggap ada bisnis disitu “apa-apa kok dibisniskan, padahal semuanya benar benar bisnis”, padahal semuanya bisnis Bisnis adalah kegiatan creating value — menciptakan nilai. Maka dari itu bisnis profit dan ada juga yang non profit, seperti kegiatan keorganisasian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curhat Tentang Lembaga Dakwah</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-03-14-saran-untuk-fuki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-03-14-saran-untuk-fuki/</guid>
      <description>Keresahan saya setelah menjalani organisasi bercorak muslim (DKM SMAN 4 Bdg, HIROKOBA, terutama FUKI Fasilkom UI) Masalah utama organisasi adalah tidak mengetahui masalahnya apa, akhirnya bikin program tidak terlalu penting kemudian semua anggotanya dipaksa untuk ikut program Visi misi nilai dijadikan formalitas belaka.
Tidak fokus ke program yang benar-benar berdampak dan sesuai kapasitas kapabilitas anggota.
Tidak berani menstop program yang dirasa kurang jelas.
Semua divisi menjalankan programnya masing-masing, dan partisipan aktifnya hanyalah anggota divisi itu sendiri.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ouija</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-20-ouija/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 10:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-20-ouija/</guid>
      <description>When I was in the last year of Junior High School, I forgot about the details of the event actually because it was 3 years before. I forgot why at that time the upper stairs were unoccupied. I forgot about the number of my friends that come there. I only remember the three of us were playing this game and the feeling of being moved by ‘something&#39;.
There were groups that talked about something that they had never experienced before, and they assembled talking about that and made me and my friends curious about that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Comedy ~ Part 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 12:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-5/</guid>
      <description>Narrated from Ibn Umar Radhiyallahu anhu, the Prophet sallallaahu &amp;lsquo;alaihi wa sallam said:
كُلُّ مُسْكِرٍ خَمْرٌ ، وَكُلُّ مُسْكِرٍ حَرَامٌ
Everything intoxicating is khamr, and everything that is intoxicating is haram. [Reported by Muslim].
The simple thing about this, it brings many benefits, but the harm is bigger than the benefits.
We can see that alcoholists who are drunk are always doing something out of our reach. A few accidents are caused by being drunk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Comedy ~ Part 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 11:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-4/</guid>
      <description>This is the other example which I think is part of the law of comedy too,
اللَّهُمَّ إلَّا أَنْ يَكُونَ فِي سَمَاعِهِ ضَرَرٌ دِينِيٌّ لَا يَنْدَفِعُ إلَّا بِالسَّدِّ
&amp;ldquo;By Allah, even listening to a chant (or a musical instrument) is a terrible danger to one&amp;rsquo;s religion, there is no other way than to block the path so as not to hear it.&amp;rdquo;
From Majmu &amp;lsquo;Al Fatawa, Ahmad bin Abdul Halim Al Haroini, 11/567, Darul Wafa&amp;rsquo;, third printing, 1426 H.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Comedy ~ Part 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 11:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-3/</guid>
      <description>In the search for the law of comedy, I find the one which is closest to the system of comedy. It must contradict with everything, it must be referring to the rule of number one that we are not living, but we&amp;rsquo;re just trapped in this world.
Let&amp;rsquo;s just take a look at the piece of the rule of comedy which I found interesting .
إنَّ الَّذينَ يصنَعونَ هذِه الصُّوَرَ يعذَّبونَ يومَ القيامةِ ، يقالُ لَهم: أحيوا ما خلقتُمْ</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Comedy ~ Part 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-2/</guid>
      <description>My biases always search for the law of comedy which is universal. And it is never constructed against the law of comedy. Left wing or right wing, poor or rich, conservative or liberal, socialism or communism, everything looks different because of the word &amp;ldquo;or&amp;rdquo;. If every &amp;ldquo;or&amp;rdquo; of them combine with &amp;ldquo;and&amp;rdquo; then everything actually has no different from them, any of them always leads to something the same, which is the output of law comedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Comedy ~ Part 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 11:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Considered I am a conservative or democratic or liberal or anything, because actually any typology of ideology, everything is all the same.
It is categorized and classified because they didn&amp;rsquo;t really know what lies in the idea that seems opposite with them.
It&amp;rsquo;s like the MBTI, the typology of personality.
Why people or any students who struggle in continuing their career or life trust about this typology even though it is full of biases is because they didn&amp;rsquo;t really know about that thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kekonyolan Sertifikasi Dai Kemenag</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-15-blunder-kemenag/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-15-blunder-kemenag/</guid>
      <description>https://news.detik.com/berita/d-5168493/cerita-di-balik-kontroversi-sertifikasi-dai-kemenag---mui
Kelompok lain sudah menggunakan kecerdasan buatan (AI) untuk memanipulasi data dan psikologi massa dalam rangka memenangkan pemilu. Namun, pada saat yang sama, kita tengah menghadapi perpecahan di antara rakyat menggunakan metode sertifikasi yang beragam. Semua ini terjadi di tengah situasi pandemi yang lebih memperburuk keadaan. Saya mengerti bahwa tujuannya mungkin ingin meredakan perbedaan pendapat, tetapi seolah-olah kita sedang menciptakan masalah yang lebih besar di masa depan dengan menciptakan ketegangan yang lebih besar di antara kelompok-kelompok yang berbeda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islam dan Nihilisme</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-07-29-islam-dan-nihilisme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-07-29-islam-dan-nihilisme/</guid>
      <description>Islam dan nihilisme memang bertentangan, tapi di setiap pertentangan pastilah ada sesuatu kesamaan yang tidak dapat dilihat apabila hanya &amp;ldquo;satu&amp;rdquo; yang dilihat.
Setiap yang berkecukupan secara materi mencari sesuatu yang lebih dan itulah yang saya lakukan untuk menutupi apa yang disebut sebagai kekosongan. Bahagia adalah sesuatu yang mudah dalam hidup sehingga bukanlah suatu yang perlu dibanggakan untuk menaruhnya ke dalam kekosongan.
Untuk menemukan sesuatu yang kosong itu diperlukan suatu keberanian. Dari sedikit keberanian seorang penakut murni mungkin didapati setelahnya adalah kesombongan yang apabila diliat dari seorang penakut lainnya adalah suatu kemegahan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim condition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-07-06-muslim-condition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-07-06-muslim-condition/</guid>
      <description>2 years ago I was having an opportunity to be a Chief Of Badan Syiar Media (BSM) Division in HIROKOBA(Association of Muslim Teenage in Bandung Area) but actually its more like a nephotism because I don&amp;rsquo;t really have an experienced about media, such as visual design, article writing, movie making, and public relation with social media.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I accepted the request from my friend maybe because it seems easy because to be a leader you don&amp;rsquo;t have to have a technical skill and such those things.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-05-24-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 11:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-05-24-intro/</guid>
      <description>وَإِذْ قَالَ رَبُّكَ لِلْمَلَٰٓئِكَةِ إِنِّى جَاعِلٌ فِى ٱلْأَرْضِ خَلِيفَةً ۖ قَالُوٓا۟ أَتَجْعَلُ فِيهَا مَن يُفْسِدُ فِيهَا وَيَسْفِكُ ٱلدِّمَآءَ وَنَحْنُ نُسَبِّحُ بِحَمْدِكَ وَنُقَدِّسُ لَكَ ۖ قَالَ إِنِّىٓ أَعْلَمُ مَا لَا تَعْلَمُونَ
˹Remember˺ when your Lord said to the angels, &amp;ldquo;I am going to place a successive ˹human˺ authority on earth.&amp;rdquo; They asked ˹Allah˺, &amp;ldquo;Will You place in it someone who will spread corruption there and shed blood while we glorify Your praises and proclaim Your holiness?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History of this blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-05-19-history-of-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-05-19-history-of-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Da steh ich nun, ich armer Tor, und bin so klug als wie zuvor.&amp;rdquo;
― Johann Wolfgang von Goethe
It&amp;rsquo;s Eid Al-Fitr, 5 days ago 19 years, it&amp;rsquo;s gone crazy because of the pandemic. Lots of assignments, 2 weeks off and I&amp;rsquo;m still lazy but lazy to study even though 23 credits and many materials have been forgotten
Finally I&amp;rsquo;m wasting my time playing ML, PUBG, hacking cellphones, installing custom roms, theming substratum, flowdor, reading crime and punishment but bored, after Ramadhan worship suddenly lazy, watching Bungou Stray Dogs is over and lazy to watch others, watching youtube harvest moon, bathing cows, mukbang, tedtalk, philosophy, rumaysho, sadhguru, psycothis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Referensi Bitcoin (archieved)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-02-09-referensi-bitcoin-archieved/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-02-09-referensi-bitcoin-archieved/</guid>
      <description>Whitepapernya banyak yg niat bngt
https://www.islamicfinanceguru.com/investment/scholars-who-say-cryptocurrency-is-haram-and-those-who-say-its-halal/
https://kumparan.com/kumparannews/11-poin-mui-tentang-bitcoin-yang-diharamkan-sebagai-investasi/full
tinggal nunggu bubblenya pecah, atau taunya diterima sama mayoritas trs jadi mata uang stabil
https://coinmarketcap.com/alexandria/article/tesla-buys-1-5-billion-in-bitcoin-and-will-accept-crypto-as-a-payment-method-soon
https://pintu.co.id/blog/perusahaan-retail-dunia-yang-terima-pembayaran-dengan-bitcoin
https://www.cnbcindonesia.com/tech/20210122165558-37-218110/perusahaan-teknologi-ini-bayar-gaji-karyawan-pakai-bitcoin-cs
https://www.cnbcindonesia.com/syariah/20180718151108-29-24182/mata-uang-digital-ini-dapat-sertifikasi-halal-dari-bahrain
https://www.cnbcindonesia.com/tech/20210208133047-37-221849/china-getol-uji-uang-digital-yuan-lawan-bitcoin-ini-buktinya
liberdancean vs konserpatip
https://www.libertarianism.org/essays/libertarian-vision-for-cryptocurrencies
https://www.thebalance.com/is-bitcoin-the-answer-in-a-financial-crisis-391275
https://www.ft.com/content/eeeacd7c-2e0e-11e9-ba00-0251022932c8
https://kumparan.com/andri-rahmad-wijaya/bitcoin-antara-kemajuan-teknologi-dan-krisis-ekonomi/full
https://konsultasisyariah.com/31095-bitcoin-itu-dilarang-koreksi-artikel-bitcoin.html
https://hackernoon.com/is-the-free-market-possible-with-a-blockchain-powered-economy-ae259cfd3eb9
Kalo cryptocurrency bisa ngilangin keberadaan umaro, apakah nanti market = umaro?
Pemerintah, industri perbankan, pihak yg punya otoritas, dan sejenisnya.
defi
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Decentralized_finance
https://www.cnnindonesia.com/ekonomi/20180115175339-78-269063/bank-indonesia-sebut-bitcoin-bisa-ganggu-stabilitas-keuangan
https://www.forbes.com/sites/shehanchandrasekera/2021/01/11/how-are-cryptocurrencies-taxed/?sh=74fe4b506812
https://www.merdeka.com/uang/dari-bos-bi-hingga-sri-mulyani-ingatkan-bitcoin-tidak-boleh-digunakan-untuk-investasi.html
https://www.researchgate.net/publication/333388187_Sex_Drugs_and_Bitcoin_How_Much_Illegal_Activity_Is_Financed_through_Cryptocurrencies
https://www.hmetro.com.my/itmetro/2019/10/502491/mudarat-wang-kripto
https://www.prescouter.com/2018/11/will-bitcoin-be-the-worlds-single-currency-in-10-years/
https://www.safepal.io/
https://www.pajak.go.id/id/artikel/polemik-antara-regulasi-pemerintah-dan-virtual-currency
santi said japanese people prefer &amp;ldquo;how you make money&amp;rdquo; than &amp;ldquo;how much money you make&amp;rdquo;,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Islamic Dawah and Go to Hell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-01-12-about-islamic-dakwah-and-go-to-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 11:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-01-12-about-islamic-dakwah-and-go-to-hell/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Tact is the ability to tell someone to go to hell in such a way that they look forward to the trip.&amp;rdquo;
― Winston Churchill
Successful dawah occurs when the person being preached truly fears hell.
Therefore, every preacher is a businessman, because they are negotiators. When the preacher cannot negotiate, what happens is only the failure of the dawah.
And the successful negotiation of the preacher is the moment of convincing the preacher that they will go to hell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idul Adha: Pantaskah kita meneriakkan Allahu Akbar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2017-09-01-idul-adha-allahu-akbar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2017-09-01-idul-adha-allahu-akbar/</guid>
      <description>Idul Adha, sering kali dianggap hanya sebagai ritual berkurban hewan dan berbagi daging. Namun, apakah kita benar-benar memahami makna mendalam di balik perayaan ini? Mari kita renungkan dan pertanyakan sejauh mana kesadaran kita terhadap kehendak Allah dalam setiap tindakan kita.
Jika Idul Fitri melambangkan kesucian, maka Idul Adha bermakna sebagai kembalinya semangat pengorbanan. Apa yang sebenarnya terkandung dalam makna &amp;ldquo;kurban&amp;rdquo;? Kata &amp;ldquo;kurban&amp;rdquo; sendiri berasal dari bahasa Arab yang mengandung arti mendekatkan diri kepada Allah.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissonance of Religious Practice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2018-06-06-dissonance-of-religious-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2018-06-06-dissonance-of-religious-practice/</guid>
      <description>There are some individuals on this Earth who, during the Islamic month of Ramadan, behave like donkeys. They read what they do not understand and persist in reading what is seemingly impossible for them to comprehend. Hundreds of pages, even until the end, remain devoid of meaning to them, and their foolishness persists, even though they do not grasp the essence of their reading. They continue to repeat it from chapter one to the final chapter because their teacher claimed that reading a single letter holds the value of ten virtues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manifesto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2001-01-01-masjid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2001-01-01-masjid/</guid>
      <description>بسم الله الرحمن الرحيم
Akselerasi Smart City Melalui Masjid Berprestasi Keywords Social Credit System, Sistem Organisasi Masyarakat, Sistem Pendidikan, Akselerasi Smart City
Abstrak Pembuatan Social Credit System di tingkat individu dan Sistem Organisasi Masyarakat di ruang lingkup masyarakat.
Latar Belakang Infrastruktur sudah tersedia, namun belum dimanfaatkan secara optimal. Dengan jumlah masjid mencapai sekitar 800.000 di Indonesia, masih banyak masjid yang belum aktif atau tidak memiliki kegiatan terkait teknologi dan keberlanjutan manusia.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
