<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pseudocomedy on Laataiasu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/pseudocomedy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pseudocomedy on Laataiasu</description>
    <image>
      <title>Laataiasu</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 12:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/pseudocomedy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Comedy ~ Part 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 12:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-5/</guid>
      <description>Narrated from Ibn Umar Radhiyallahu anhu, the Prophet sallallaahu &amp;lsquo;alaihi wa sallam said:
كُلُّ مُسْكِرٍ خَمْرٌ ، وَكُلُّ مُسْكِرٍ حَرَامٌ
Everything intoxicating is khamr, and everything that is intoxicating is haram. [Reported by Muslim].
The simple thing about this, it brings many benefits, but the harm is bigger than the benefits.
We can see that alcoholists who are drunk are always doing something out of our reach. A few accidents are caused by being drunk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Comedy ~ Part 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 11:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-4/</guid>
      <description>This is the other example which I think is part of the law of comedy too,
اللَّهُمَّ إلَّا أَنْ يَكُونَ فِي سَمَاعِهِ ضَرَرٌ دِينِيٌّ لَا يَنْدَفِعُ إلَّا بِالسَّدِّ
&amp;ldquo;By Allah, even listening to a chant (or a musical instrument) is a terrible danger to one&amp;rsquo;s religion, there is no other way than to block the path so as not to hear it.&amp;rdquo;
From Majmu &amp;lsquo;Al Fatawa, Ahmad bin Abdul Halim Al Haroini, 11/567, Darul Wafa&amp;rsquo;, third printing, 1426 H.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Comedy ~ Part 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 11:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-3/</guid>
      <description>In the search for the law of comedy, I find the one which is closest to the system of comedy. It must contradict with everything, it must be referring to the rule of number one that we are not living, but we&amp;rsquo;re just trapped in this world.
Let&amp;rsquo;s just take a look at the piece of the rule of comedy which I found interesting .
إنَّ الَّذينَ يصنَعونَ هذِه الصُّوَرَ يعذَّبونَ يومَ القيامةِ ، يقالُ لَهم: أحيوا ما خلقتُمْ</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Comedy ~ Part 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 11:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-2/</guid>
      <description>My biases always search for the law of comedy which is universal. And it is never constructed against the law of comedy. Left wing or right wing, poor or rich, conservative or liberal, socialism or communism, everything looks different because of the word &amp;ldquo;or&amp;rdquo;. If every &amp;ldquo;or&amp;rdquo; of them combine with &amp;ldquo;and&amp;rdquo; then everything actually has no different from them, any of them always leads to something the same, which is the output of law comedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Law of Comedy ~ Part 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 11:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-15-law-of-comedy-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Considered I am a conservative or democratic or liberal or anything, because actually any typology of ideology, everything is all the same.
It is categorized and classified because they didn&amp;rsquo;t really know what lies in the idea that seems opposite with them.
It&amp;rsquo;s like the MBTI, the typology of personality.
Why people or any students who struggle in continuing their career or life trust about this typology even though it is full of biases is because they didn&amp;rsquo;t really know about that thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replaced</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-14-replaced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 05:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-14-replaced/</guid>
      <description>The greatest form of usefulness is to make many people lose their usefulness. In this way, those who lose their usefulness turn to those who enjoy it.
In the Management course, I ask my lecturer. &amp;ldquo;If technical workers been replaced by AI, it means that the technical business process is fulfilled and there will be no problems again in the technical sector so that low-level manager is not needed anymore. If it is fulfilled the effective, efficient, and productive in business, can it be developed until the high-level manager, the director, or CEO be replaced by Robots?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choice Blindness</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-24-choice-blindness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 11:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-24-choice-blindness/</guid>
      <description>Teknologi mengedit dan menghapus kenangan manusia
Looking at the source above might make a little amazement at the development of science. That is, the development of the product and that theory can solve many neurological problems. But this is just the first step towards creating something &amp;ldquo;more&amp;rdquo; than this.
If we let ourselves think fictionally, or it&amp;rsquo;s not fiction after all, what happened in a lot of science fiction films or books can happen in real life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waking Up an Outdated Version of Intelligence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-18-waking-up-an-outdated-version-of-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 15:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-18-waking-up-an-outdated-version-of-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>The ultimate goal of every living being is to rest.
So when sentient beings try to work,
effectiveness, efficiency, or productivity will never be achieved.
Because everything is only leads to rest.
So when a living being feels the need to work,
when actually his true self is just a rest,
all of that will bring up the peculiarity.
And peculiarities will always lead to gaps.
So when a man has a feeling needed to work,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissonance of Religious Practice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2018-06-06-dissonance-of-religious-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2018-06-06-dissonance-of-religious-practice/</guid>
      <description>There are some individuals on this Earth who, during the Islamic month of Ramadan, behave like donkeys. They read what they do not understand and persist in reading what is seemingly impossible for them to comprehend. Hundreds of pages, even until the end, remain devoid of meaning to them, and their foolishness persists, even though they do not grasp the essence of their reading. They continue to repeat it from chapter one to the final chapter because their teacher claimed that reading a single letter holds the value of ten virtues.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
