<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Book on Laataiasu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/book/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book on Laataiasu</description>
    <image>
      <title>Laataiasu</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review How Do You Live</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-12-09-how-do-you-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-12-09-how-do-you-live/</guid>
      <description>the lesson learned from copper, uragawa, mizutani, kitami stories, and pram&amp;rsquo;s works in general, is that it projects that your kids can only choose to become:
the bully, the one who is being bullied, and the one who only watches when a bullying event happens. when you see land seized, genocide, warfare in a certain place, how lifeless technologies snatch jobs from luddites, the ignorance of workers who feel irreplaceable not engaging in long-term solutions to encourage capital owners to implement aspects of justice, poor-quality food, unsanitary living conditions, working day after day, galactic collisions, tidal interactions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Anxiety When Dining Alone in Restaurants</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-09-16-anxiety-when-eating-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-09-16-anxiety-when-eating-alone/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve come to understand concepts like the &amp;lsquo;spotlight effect,&amp;rsquo; delved into the intriguing depths of &amp;lsquo;The Mind Explained&amp;rsquo; Netflix series, and engaged with content that reminds us of our shared humanity in this vast world.
The phrase &amp;ldquo;kullu nafsin daikotul maut&amp;rdquo; resonates, reminding us that every soul will face mortality. Then there&amp;rsquo;s YOLO, the philosophy of seizing the day, and the notion of entropy and complexity, which rise with the passage of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silenus dan Kebahagiaan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-09-02-silenus-dan-kebahagiaan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-09-02-silenus-dan-kebahagiaan/</guid>
      <description>Raja Midas mencari Silenus, teman setia Dionysus, dan menanyakan kepadanya: &amp;ldquo;Apa kebahagiaan terbesar manusia?&amp;rdquo; Silenus tetap muram dan tidak berkomunikasi sampai akhirnya, dipaksa oleh Raja, ia tertawa dengan kencang.
&amp;ldquo;Manusia yang fanatis, lahir karena kecelakaan dan ketekunan, mengapa kamu memaksakanku untuk memberitahu apa yang akan menjadi kebahagiaan terbesarmu yang seharusnya kamu tidak ingin mengetahui? Yang terbaik bagimu adalah tidak pernah dilahirkan. Yang kedua terbaik adalah mati segera!&amp;rdquo;
Bagaimana budaya Hellenik menanggung kebenaran yang mengerikan ini?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kino no Tabi, Job Hopping and The Modern Nomad</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-08-05-kino-no-tabi-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-08-05-kino-no-tabi-review/</guid>
      <description>Job hopping resembles the traveler&amp;rsquo;s journey in Kino&amp;rsquo;s travels in &amp;ldquo;Kino no Tabi.&amp;rdquo; Traveling seems to be a dream shared by many, akin to creating a legacy like Ibn Battuta and others did in previous generations. However, this notion appears outdated now due to the advent of tools like Google Maps. While such tools cover most places, some areas remain uncharted, and they fail to capture the true ambiance and local behavior, or in a places like China might lack comprehensive map reviews due to strict government policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Quadrants of Optimism and Pessimism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-04-24-four-quadrant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-04-24-four-quadrant/</guid>
      <description>In this contemplative discourse, we delve into the intricacies of various outlooks on life, aiming to shed light on the complexities that define our existence. Inspired by Peter Thiel&amp;rsquo;s concept of the four quadrants of optimism, we embark on a journey to understand where we stand.
1. Definite Pessimism: The Doomer&amp;rsquo;s Realm
Many find themselves in this quadrant, resonating with the likes of Greta Thunberg, immersing in the world of AI, and pondering over films such as &amp;lsquo;The Social Dilemma&amp;rsquo; (though, admittedly, the sound design can be somewhat unsettling).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review NNT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-01-23-review-nnt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-01-23-review-nnt/</guid>
      <description>black swan
anti fragile
skin in the game
bed of procustes
titik balik ga? gatau anying hoream, masih banyak downsidenya dibanding upside, masih coward, mau ttp diteken apa jadi asshole? gatau aokwoakwoakwok idiot sumpah ini asshole nikolas taleb.
kenapa aing suka bukunya? ada nietzsche, nyinggung alghazali, ibnu rusydi, mitologi yunani aneh-aneh, plato, filsafat tapi trader dan statistik cok, kurang seru apa coba. wibu nerd anjing ga guna sampah masyarakat, lebanon katanya penuh perang, kakeknya gubernur, tapi dapet gawe gimana caranya.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humor and Love Part 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-12-10-humor-and-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-12-10-humor-and-love/</guid>
      <description>Always forgot about this, but this Letters to a Young Contrarian by Christopher Hitchens from an atheist dissilutionizing me that whatever your condition is, you need a t least add a humour to that condition. I aware of this things actually, from
, and from One Flew Over the Cuckoo&amp;rsquo;s Nest that said like this,
&amp;ldquo;Man, when you lose your laugh you lose your footing.&amp;rdquo;
I hope that my previos writting has a component of humor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review The Death of Expertise by Tom Nichols</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-08-28-review-the-death-of-expertise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-08-28-review-the-death-of-expertise/</guid>
      <description>Looking for a friend who has the same vision as me. The problem is I never have a static view of something called principles. Sometimes I contradict myself, to stand by one vision and principles, but I never did that. That’s why It’s so hard for me to find a friend, friend based on my definition. But I never describe what a friend is. It’s always just intuition that sometimes I know that it fits with us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review A Guide to Wealth and Happiness — Naval Ravikant</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-08-28-naval-ravikant-a-guide-to-wealth-and-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-08-28-naval-ravikant-a-guide-to-wealth-and-happiness/</guid>
      <description>ringkasan buku investor artis twitter
Konsumsi konten self-improvement biasanya membuat saya jijik dan eneg, tapi yang ini rasanya beda.
Mungkin karena kebetulan backgroundnya cukup saya minati,
computer science ekonomi investasi crypto pemalas Ilmunya menurut saya aplikatif dimana-mana dan ga terbatas pada bidang2 itu
Yang paling menonjol mungkin tentang:
&amp;ldquo;How to Get Rich Without Getting Lucky&amp;rdquo;
Gabisa dibuat ringkasannya karena menurut saya materinya udah padat. Kalo ga ada waktu mungkin bisa baca highlight tweetnya doang</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review Start-up Nation — Dan Senor and Saul Singer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-08-28-startup-nation-israel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-08-28-startup-nation-israel/</guid>
      <description>Buku yang menurut saya intro dan conclusionnya wajib dibaca oleh seluruh goyim
Banyak propagandanya. Nevertheless, just learn to love being tricked and learn what can be learned Awal 2007
Shai Agassi (Nulis paper tentang mobil listrik, mantan top executive SAP), ada hubungannya dengan Shimon Peres untuk inisiasi negara, cari car company, n biaya.
Ingin menjadi negara pertama yang ingin bebas dari bahan bakar minyak
Kenapa percobaan mobil listrik pertama di israel?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review Liar&#39;s Poker by Michael Lewis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-08-27-michael-lewis-liars-poker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-08-27-michael-lewis-liars-poker/</guid>
      <description>ringkasan buku mantan asosial gambler
Awal mulanya dari nonton Big Short, film tentang krisis tahun 2008
Filmnya diadaptasi dari buku-buku Michael Lewis, buku2 lainnya juga bagus
Rekomendasi M. Burry, yang prediksi krisis itu:
Gakuat baca sampai habis, ringkasan ini lumayan lengkap:
https://www.allencheng.com/liars-poker-book-summary-michael-lewis/
Ringkasannya Kebobrokan korporasi keuangan, khususnya broker jaman 80 90an dulu di US. Dia pernah jadi salah satu banking investment anlyst, lebih spesifik lagi jadi bond trader, gatau lah apaan itu Diceritain proses masuknya, kemunafikan proses recruitmennya, saling menjatuhkan antara kandidat, tentang MBA, dll Banyak hikmah yang bisa diambil, salah satunya cheat dr warcraft III,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review Zero to One by Peter Thiel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-08-21-peter-thiel-zero-to-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-08-21-peter-thiel-zero-to-one/</guid>
      <description>Chapternya pendek-pendek jadi ga terlalu ngebosenin, cerita-ceritanya lumayan asik.
Nih… Make startup with few people, not too few and not too big Creative monopoly — dont compete with other market, but create your own market &amp;ldquo;the more we compete, the less we gain&amp;rdquo; Competition is devastated, if you can&amp;rsquo;t beat rival it may be better to merge Characteristics of monopoly:
Propietary technology, Network effects, Economies of scale, Branding Building monopoly:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why This Earth Of Mankind Is A Dangerous Book</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-12-19-why-this-earth-of-mankind-is-a-dangerous-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 18:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-12-19-why-this-earth-of-mankind-is-a-dangerous-book/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s praise the old Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s government who succeeded at doctrined the boomer generations or in their length of service about the danger of communism.
Including one of the books banned from circulation at that period, namely &amp;ldquo;Bumi Manusia&amp;rdquo;.
It&amp;rsquo;s actually quite strange when we see that the book was banned during the Soeharto&amp;rsquo;s period because of indications of communism there. But after I looked further, the government in the past was really clever and genius.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review The Most Horror Webtoon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-09-review-horror-manhwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-09-review-horror-manhwa/</guid>
      <description>So this is my review for the most horror manhwa I&amp;rsquo;ve ever read. Most horror in manhwa never feels like horror, actually. I am a fainthearted seriously. I always act like am a brave person whenever I watch movies with friends in my childhood, and after I went home, I often had a hard time to sleep and go to some room of my house in the night because I was very scared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review Daerah Salju Yasunari Kawabata</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-07-29-review-daerah-salju-yasunari-kawabata/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 01:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-07-29-review-daerah-salju-yasunari-kawabata/</guid>
      <description>Roman fiksi pertama yang w baca dengan serius wkwkwk.
Awal baca ini taun kemarin sebenernya pas lagi gabut di rumah sodara nunggu ujian utul UGM. W beli dari toko di line paket 3 buku, yaitu ini, Meatspace, sama cerita detektif. Penasaran karena menang nobel kesusastraan jadi w baca ini dengan cepet pas di Jogja beberapa hari beres, terus&amp;hellip;
&amp;ldquo;Hah? kok bisa menang ya? B aja perasaan, ya walaupun ada quotes ala-ala realist yang lumayan sih&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; dan w tutup itu buku dengan perasaan kecewa&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
