<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Film on Laataiasu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/film/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Film on Laataiasu</description>
    <image>
      <title>Laataiasu</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:23:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/film/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review All of Us Strangers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2024-02-25-review-moriarty-x-connell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2024-02-25-review-moriarty-x-connell/</guid>
      <description>i hate gay people.
no matter how i try to understand them, through watching movies, i just can&amp;rsquo;t empathy with them.
i never relate, i can&amp;rsquo;t understand how they process to have feeling for each other.
in sex scenes, i still find them disgusting.
i don&amp;rsquo;t know maybe im just bias towards this because lightning stroke in my room at 1 AM right now.
maybe im just afraid of that lightning that makes me hate gay people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Anxiety When Dining Alone in Restaurants</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-09-16-anxiety-when-eating-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-09-16-anxiety-when-eating-alone/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve come to understand concepts like the &amp;lsquo;spotlight effect,&amp;rsquo; delved into the intriguing depths of &amp;lsquo;The Mind Explained&amp;rsquo; Netflix series, and engaged with content that reminds us of our shared humanity in this vast world.
The phrase &amp;ldquo;kullu nafsin daikotul maut&amp;rdquo; resonates, reminding us that every soul will face mortality. Then there&amp;rsquo;s YOLO, the philosophy of seizing the day, and the notion of entropy and complexity, which rise with the passage of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kino no Tabi, Job Hopping and The Modern Nomad</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-08-05-kino-no-tabi-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-08-05-kino-no-tabi-review/</guid>
      <description>Job hopping resembles the traveler&amp;rsquo;s journey in Kino&amp;rsquo;s travels in &amp;ldquo;Kino no Tabi.&amp;rdquo; Traveling seems to be a dream shared by many, akin to creating a legacy like Ibn Battuta and others did in previous generations. However, this notion appears outdated now due to the advent of tools like Google Maps. While such tools cover most places, some areas remain uncharted, and they fail to capture the true ambiance and local behavior, or in a places like China might lack comprehensive map reviews due to strict government policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Or You Live Long Enough To See Yourself Become Meme, or Running a White Woman&#39;s Instagram</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-07-10-administrasi-lambat-cimahi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-07-10-administrasi-lambat-cimahi/</guid>
      <description>Terima kasih @CimahiSamsat atas pelayanannya saya bisa nonton 2 film dokumenter indo komedi ini
The Act of Killing (2012)
The Look of Silence (2014)
&amp;ldquo;Cinema is the ultimate pervert art. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t give you what you desire - it tells you how to desire.&amp;rdquo;
Sedikit antidote buat doomer/gloomer/dkk adalah nonton mujahid hasil karya CCP
Just accept, jangan cari tau prosesnya, nonton hewan lucu + dagelan aja, internet surfing is bidah. Top gun, forrest gump, dll adalah propraganda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Luffy is the Authentic Hegelian Master</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-07-07-authenticity-only-for-ignorant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-07-07-authenticity-only-for-ignorant/</guid>
      <description>Authenticity is bullshit. Make a sign and hide! Don&amp;rsquo;t show! Don&amp;rsquo;t tell!
You can&amp;rsquo;t be authentic if you&amp;rsquo;re not ignorant.
Only the indifferent and ignorant can be authentic.
That explains why Luffy from One Piece is the authentic Hegelian master. He is as innocent as a child, simply wanting to be free, the best version of himself, and the pirate king. The plot itself is perfect.
He lives his life in ignorance and cannot die because it&amp;rsquo;s the main character&amp;rsquo;s superpower from the author.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sympathy for the Devil: Empathy for the Rich and Powerful in a Complex Society</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-05-19-sympathy-for-the-devil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-05-19-sympathy-for-the-devil/</guid>
      <description>Flexing, greed, pride, arrogance, and vanity are merely perceptions projected by those who feel inferior and envious. In the words of Charlie Munger, the world is driven by envy, not greed.
Every advantage should be appreciated. When does gratitude become excessive? It is only those who envy that impose limits on gratitude. One form of gratitude is sharing fortune and abundance, being free from hunger, having positive relationships with family and friends, possessing material and physical advantages, embodying good morals and spirituality, showcasing talents and creations, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islam and the Data Scientist&#39;s Quest: Seeking Insights Amidst Biases and Mental Models</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-03-01-muslim-and-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-03-01-muslim-and-data-science/</guid>
      <description>data scientist dan the sixth sense movie
&amp;ldquo;I see dead people walking around like regular people, they don&amp;rsquo;t know the are dead&amp;rdquo;
Paranoid, banyak asumsi, banyak interpretasi, ujung-ujungnya simplifikasi sesuatu yang kompleks.
Dari dulu diajarin buat selalu cari pola, cari makna
padahal it&amp;rsquo;s obvious, ga ada makna.
art of clear thinking, daniel kahnemann bias,
sadar bahwa defaultnya manusia itu emang tolol, penuh bias.
Biases arose because they are effective. And effectiveness has always been a virtue favorable to survival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humor and Love Part 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-02-23-humor-and-love-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-02-23-humor-and-love-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Aku ini orang mati. Siapa yang bertanggung jawab saat aku lepas kendali. Apakah kendali diri itu nyata? Aku selalu mencari alasan dibalik suatu kemungkinan terburuk yang pernah terjadi. Carpe diem, bisikan setan itu lah yang selalu memaksaku bertindak konyol. Aku ini pengecut, yang tidak berani mati. Begitu hampanya malaikat karena tidak bernafsu, maka nafsu ini suatu anugrah yang hanya untuk manusia bukan? Bila menjadi manusia adalah menjadi bernafsu, maka untuk apa aku tahan semua ini.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Turkey Problem in Gen-Z</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-02-01-turkey-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 11:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-02-01-turkey-problem/</guid>
      <description>Generation Z is often seen as carefree, facing difficulty in finding jobs, lacking respect for adults, being oversensitive yet savage and brutal, experiencing sexual weaknesses, engaging in deception through social media, adopting a borrowing mentality, having a short attention span, challenging the status quo, dealing with information overload, being exposed to excessive news about corruption, participating in cancel culture, and facing the consequences of global warming. They often associate various issues with mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chunking Express: Betapa Culasnya Sentuhan Kehidupan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-01-13-review-chunking-express/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2023-01-13-review-chunking-express/</guid>
      <description>Saya jadi ingat nangis kejer-kejer setelah menonton Chungking Express yang sebenarnya tidak ada adegan sedihnya sama sekali. Kesendirian kronis itu seperti bom waktu dan cara menjinakkannya secara sementara adalah dengan berpura-pura menjadi tuhan atau binatang. Bahwa kata-kata itu busuk dan tidak ada gunanya, setiap kode yang ditampilkan melalui gerak bicara juga sia-sia belaka.
Saat kepedulian si Faye tertangkap basah, maka betapa malu rasanya yang menampakkannya. Pada dasarnya keiklasan dari rasa peduli itu muncul dari gejolak ketakutan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Susah Cari Kerja</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-07-06--susah-nyari-kerja/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 17:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-07-06--susah-nyari-kerja/</guid>
      <description>Cari Magang Kuliah Selama liburan semester ini, saya berusaha mencari magang untuk meningkatkan pengalaman. Meskipun sebenarnya saya berharap tidak harus magang karena masih memiliki banyak tugas dan film yang jadi todolist. Tapi bohong, saya hanya menolak menerima kenyataan bahwa mendapatkan magang sangat sulit. Meskipun telah mengikuti beberapa wawancara, belum ada hasil yang memuaskan.
Keberadaan berbagai platform pencari kerja sebenarnya tidak membantu, malah membuat kebingungan karena terlalu banyak pilihan ~ paradox of choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost/Phantom: A Harrowing Reflection on Corruption, Media Sensationalism, and the Vicious Cycle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-01-11-review-ghost-phantom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2022-01-11-review-ghost-phantom/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: &amp;ldquo;Ghost/Phantom&amp;rdquo; is a Korean drama series that delves into the world of cybercrime and journalism, shedding light on the inherent corruption within society. Through its portrayal of media sensationalism and the cyclical nature of complaints and profits, the show provides a thought-provoking analysis of our collective flaws. This essay will explore these themes and their implications in contemporary society.
The Portrayal of Corruption: &amp;ldquo;Ghost/Phantom&amp;rdquo; exposes the deep-seated corruption that permeates society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmos Movie Series Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-07-27-cosmos-movie-series-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-07-27-cosmos-movie-series-review/</guid>
      <description>I. Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey Eps 1 he shown us how little we are, 100 ribu tahun cahaya from the milky way galaxy
1599 cant look into universe
copernicus, giordano bruno
Galileo galilei
II. Cosmos: Possible Worlds Eps 1, spinoza
Eps 2, Ahura mazda, buddha, Ashoka
Eps 3, goldschmit geology
Eps 4, Vavilov, darwin, lamark
Eps 5, hippocrates : father of medicine, angelo mosso, brain, neuroscience, connectome
Eps 6, kuiper, sputnik, ecology, carl sagan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley Series Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-07-15-silicon-valley-series-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 11:42:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-07-15-silicon-valley-series-review/</guid>
      <description>The worst comedy series I&amp;rsquo;ve ever watched.
Irrelevant for me but still can be related to my perspective of my life. The geeks, the nerds, with asperger syndrome whose name is Richard. But yup like any other characters, it&amp;rsquo;s not fair if it&amp;rsquo;s only filled with misfortune, so the director or the writer add the advantages to his character which include he is the best programmer in his circle.
I don&amp;rsquo;t want to describe all, you could read it somewhere about the synopsis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin &amp; Breaking Bad</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-02-15-bitcoin-breaking-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-02-15-bitcoin-breaking-bad/</guid>
      <description>TLDR Breaking Bad Synopsis:
Walter, a chemistry teacher and part timer at a car washer, is diagnosed with cancer and because he is poor, he didn&amp;#39;t want to burden his family with the treatment for his cancer. As I have mentioned in the previous article, the feeling of weakness is pretty bad. It is caused a lot of evils and will to power is what is good for ordinary people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short-Term Profit of &#39;From Up on Poppy Hill&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-02-09-short-term-profit-of-from-up-on-poppy-hill/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 11:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-02-09-short-term-profit-of-from-up-on-poppy-hill/</guid>
      <description>I often guess something. It is strange for some people, and I am not suggesting it too. You will not get something based on guessing if you believe so. And you will get some insights, whether it is true or not, you will get insight if you believe in your guessing, which is the case for modern people nowadays.
That&amp;rsquo;s what data scientists do. Trying to get some pattern, and practical business beliefs if it could make more profit, then it is true.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Can You Not Be Romantic About Baseball?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-02-03-how-can-you-not-be-romantic-about-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 07:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-02-03-how-can-you-not-be-romantic-about-baseball/</guid>
      <description>At first, you&amp;rsquo;re afraid. You try a little bit and you get something that keeps you trying. Maybe at first you fail, then you have no idea why you didn&amp;rsquo;t fail, and after didn&amp;rsquo;t fail at such a big amount of games, you just ask, what&amp;rsquo;s the point? It is not hard to romanticize everything. Every little loss you consider as something to learn, or didn&amp;rsquo;t take something because you know that something is not gonna work, or succeed you get after you&amp;rsquo;re tryin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midsommar, The Heaven for Everyone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-01-16-midsommar-the-heaven-for-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 17:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2021-01-16-midsommar-the-heaven-for-everyone/</guid>
      <description>All environmentalist or Marxist or someone who strive for Utopia should follow this community,
There must be the will to neglect to be successful in something, ignore the mediocre. Challenging the status quo means to ignore the feeling which could come from everyone or everything. Or is this not neglect but a form of caring? Because of that, Ethics is the least important material studied in business.
Developing philanthropic businesses and green companies continues to be encouraged by every business curriculum even though this is foolishness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review Brooks, &#39;The Shawshank Redemption&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-12-13-review-brooks-the-shawshank-redemption/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 06:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-12-13-review-brooks-the-shawshank-redemption/</guid>
      <description>Without realizing it, we are always part of something. And somehow that something must always be there and be a part of us. So when something is lost or feels far from our scope, we will always feel lost.
We are trying to find something, that something is missing. But when it turns out that the thing we are looking for is not found and we are desperate, then we look for something to replace it, but when we cling to what is missing, with all our despair and reluctance to move to other things, what is lost will destroy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nosy Loli Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-12-04-review-loli-usil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 08:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-12-04-review-loli-usil/</guid>
      <description>Based on any history books, Japan colonized Indonesia for 3.5 years, from 1942 until 1945.
But it is only based on books, it probably less than that, or it probably still occurred until now.
The funny thing is The Japanese weren&amp;rsquo;t taught about Indonesia, at least from my limited resources from
The Youtuber asked 2 Japanese teenagers to guess about where he comes from and so on. And whenever he talked about Indonesia, they didn&amp;rsquo;t know anything.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Ji-Pyeong Didn&#39;t Get Dal Mi&#39;s Heart By Muslim Perspective</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-22-why-ji-pyeong-didnt-get-dal-mis-heart-by-muslim-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 20:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-22-why-ji-pyeong-didnt-get-dal-mis-heart-by-muslim-perspective/</guid>
      <description>The reasons why Ji Pyeong didn&amp;rsquo;t get Dal Mi&amp;rsquo;s heart even though he is rich:
He didn&amp;rsquo;t get the wealth in a halal way. He invests in haram companies.
Since he was an orphan, he learned to invest because he wants to be rich as fast as he can so he didn&amp;rsquo;t care about the sources of the money. He studied economy and finance but didn&amp;rsquo;t learn about sharia principles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machiavellianism in Any Educational System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-22-machiavellianism-in-the-indonesia-educational-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 03:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-22-machiavellianism-in-the-indonesia-educational-system/</guid>
      <description>Machiavellianism believes that every activity that is aimed at the stability of the country or the government is good, even if it ignores some aspects that give chaos, the act to reduce that chaos is considered &amp;lsquo;right&amp;rsquo; as long as that act is aimed to stabilize its power.
Every individual is the government of themselves. So based on Machiavellianism, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t care about the morality or in the long term which influenced the existence of any government or in the scope individual are other people, friends, family, or anyone, as long as they don&amp;rsquo;t bother the stability of the individual government, the individuals didn&amp;rsquo;t care because it only cares about its government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review Economic Films</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-10-review-econ-films/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-11-10-review-econ-films/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Big Short&amp;rdquo; delves into the complexities of the 2008 economic depression in the US, exploring terms like bubble economics and subprime mortgages. While its comedic elements may not resonate with everyone, its clear explanations make it accessible even to those unfamiliar with economic concepts, like myself.
&amp;ldquo;Beautiful Mind,&amp;rdquo; while primarily focused on John Nash&amp;rsquo;s struggle with schizophrenia, offers valuable insights into his mathematical contributions such as the Nash Equilibrium and game theory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review Se7en</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-24-review-se7en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 11:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-24-review-se7en/</guid>
      <description>There are 2 interesting terms in business, thus &amp;ldquo;standard of living&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;quality of life&amp;rdquo;
The standard of living means the amount of goods and services people can buy with the money they have.
And the quality of life means The general well-being of a society in terms of its political freedom, natural environment, education, healthcare, safety, amount of leisure, and rewards that add to personal satisfaction.
Business and their employees pay taxes to the government, Taxes help the country to build better education, facilities, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mushishi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-09-mushishi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-09-09-mushishi/</guid>
      <description>Growth mindset or whatever it is, every person can have it. But most of them (I don&amp;rsquo;t want to include myself lol) just simply can&amp;rsquo;t achieve the implementation and the realization of that mind set. It is just they can&amp;rsquo;t. Trying to be more productive, want to achieve more, programming own mind, it is really suck, especially when you are grow in environment which condong to instant gratification and not stressing something to be more meaningful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brief Review Kdrama</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-07-24-brief-review-kdrama/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 11:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-07-24-brief-review-kdrama/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s hard to strive for something and tell that something you liked to other people since a lot of them are against it. And it is much harder if you think and assume that people are against the things you liked.
&amp;ldquo;Nobody wants the things they like to be denied by others. They want other people to experience the same feeling they do. And based on that people make friends.&amp;rdquo; - Grand Blue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Network Effect Dilemma: Lessons from LinkedIn and Parasite</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2019-12-07-review-parasite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2019-12-07-review-parasite/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn, the professional networking platform, provides a glimpse into the world of marketing and self-promotion. As we navigate through various profiles, we often encounter a mix of genuine accomplishments and exaggerated self-portrayals. This experience raises intriguing questions about the nature of marketing, the network effect, and the parallels with the critically acclaimed film &amp;ldquo;Parasite.&amp;rdquo; In this essay, we will explore the lessons derived from observing LinkedIn profiles and draw connections to the network effect depicted in &amp;ldquo;Parasite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review Sixth Sense (1999)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2018-06-03-bukan-review-film-sixth-sense-1999/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 07:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2018-06-03-bukan-review-film-sixth-sense-1999/</guid>
      <description>MENGANDUNG SPOILER
Pada awalnya saya ingin mencari film drama psikologi yang bisa menitikan air mata lewat motivasinya seperti Forrest Gump atau One Flew Over Cuckoo Nest. Tapi saya rasa terlalu mainstream untuk melihat yang seperti itu, beralilahlah saya ke kaskus dan melihat rekomendasi film dengan twist ending, berkategori drama, psikologi, dan horror yang tidak lain adalah The Sixth Sense.
Cerita diawali dengan DR. Malcolm yang merupakan seorang psikolog dibunuh oleh pasiennya sendiri di rumahnya.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
