<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Intro on Laataiasu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/intro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Intro on Laataiasu</description>
    <image>
      <title>Laataiasu</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 11:43:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/intro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-05-24-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 11:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-05-24-intro/</guid>
      <description>وَإِذْ قَالَ رَبُّكَ لِلْمَلَٰٓئِكَةِ إِنِّى جَاعِلٌ فِى ٱلْأَرْضِ خَلِيفَةً ۖ قَالُوٓا۟ أَتَجْعَلُ فِيهَا مَن يُفْسِدُ فِيهَا وَيَسْفِكُ ٱلدِّمَآءَ وَنَحْنُ نُسَبِّحُ بِحَمْدِكَ وَنُقَدِّسُ لَكَ ۖ قَالَ إِنِّىٓ أَعْلَمُ مَا لَا تَعْلَمُونَ
˹Remember˺ when your Lord said to the angels, &amp;ldquo;I am going to place a successive ˹human˺ authority on earth.&amp;rdquo; They asked ˹Allah˺, &amp;ldquo;Will You place in it someone who will spread corruption there and shed blood while we glorify Your praises and proclaim Your holiness?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History of this blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-05-19-history-of-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2020-05-19-history-of-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Da steh ich nun, ich armer Tor, und bin so klug als wie zuvor.&amp;rdquo;
― Johann Wolfgang von Goethe
It&amp;rsquo;s Eid Al-Fitr, 5 days ago 19 years, it&amp;rsquo;s gone crazy because of the pandemic. Lots of assignments, 2 weeks off and I&amp;rsquo;m still lazy but lazy to study even though 23 credits and many materials have been forgotten
Finally I&amp;rsquo;m wasting my time playing ML, PUBG, hacking cellphones, installing custom roms, theming substratum, flowdor, reading crime and punishment but bored, after Ramadhan worship suddenly lazy, watching Bungou Stray Dogs is over and lazy to watch others, watching youtube harvest moon, bathing cows, mukbang, tedtalk, philosophy, rumaysho, sadhguru, psycothis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2014-01-01-awal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2014-01-01-awal/</guid>
      <description>Yooww akhirnya ane memutuskan untuk menulis blog atau (curhat di blog) nulis artikel setelah sekian lama berpikir dan ntah kenapa hati ane menggerakan jari jari seniman ini untuk menulis. Beban pikiran juga udah banyak sampe mau meledak nih otak, insomnia karena banyak mikir hal ga guna sebelum tidur jadi ane memutuskan untuk menuangkan ledakan pikiran ane disini biar semua yg ada di hati sm pikiran ane plong lalu menyusunnya serapi mungkin menjadi tulisan.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
